Welcome back to City TV with Wembley awaiting for Manchester City.
They prepare to face Arsenal in the 2026 Carabao Cup Final.
It is the Blues'fifth appearance in the showpiece event in the space of ten years under Pep Guardiola,
who was described reaching the final as an honour.
City booked their place at Wembley with a comprehensive 5 -1 aggregate victory over Holders Newcastle United in the semi -finals,
whilst Arsenal overcame Crystal Palace to set up one of the most eagerly awaited Cup finals in recent memory.
The two sides, sitting in first and second place in the league, last met in a League Cup final in 2018,
when Guardiola claimed his first piece of silverware at the club, courtesy of a convincing 3 -0 victory.
Arsenal, who have been runners -up in this competition a record six times,
will be desperate to not extend that record
and instead lift the trophy for a third time in their history.
City's recent record against the Gunners makes for fascinating reading.
Guardiola's side have not beaten Arsenal in any of their last six meetings,
a run stretching back to the famous 4 -1 triumph during the treble -winning campaign of 2022 -2023.
But Pep Guardiola has plenty of form in this competition,
and winning today will put him clear as the manager with the most League Cup wins in English football history.
We shall see if Pep can earn himself yet another record shortly.
But first of all, let's preview the game with all of the team news,
build -up and pre -match interviews from Wembley Stadium.
Thanks.
Wero, we'll find your way through here.
Sergio Aguero with a look at the hockey ball, City are in clubs in the Carabao Cup final.
Ahead of this showpiece match, we look back at the last ten goals scored
in League Cup finals by Manchester City,
The main service overturned.
And the last level, Laurel.
Demetri -3 -0.
Get out.
Thrust by Aguero.
Get the empty goal.
At the Tarabar Cup Final, spawned by Sergio Aguero.
What?
penalty spot is better made by Rodrigo.
That's two.
Full match for Senzi.
I don't know if there's no chances.
And the penalty to that.
But with the ball, scores for Senzi.
But perhaps it is enough for the card.
The manager spoke to the press in the build -up to the match.
Pep Guardiola confirmed that James Trafford would start in goal for the final,
continuing as the designated cup goalkeeper after impressing in both legs at the semi -final against Newcastle.
Josco Guardiola remains sidelined with a broken leg and will play no part at Wembley.
Mark Gay is ineligible for the contest, having arrived after the competition cut -off.
Joining them on the sidelines is Ruben Diage,
who suffered an injury in the Champions League game against Real Madrid.
In total, there are four changes from that side made by Pep Guardiola in a very attacking line -up.
That gets us up to date with the team news.
So let's head over to the Mixed Zone now,
where the cameras are waiting to pick up the pre -match interviews.
Bernardo, you've played finals, you've played big matches, won trophies with this club.
But how do you see this team in terms of maturity to play finals.
It's a good question.
We'll see.
It's a final, as you said, it's a very important game.
First trophy there.
we can win this season and we're looking forward to it.
There's been a lot of talk about City having the experience to win this trophy
and having experience to win trophies.
But how does this effectively come into play in a final?
Is it better game management or more list.
Each game is a different game.
I do believe that both teams are prepared to play this final.
We hope it goes our way today
and hopefully it's going to be a very good day for us.
We've seen this fixture have different looks.
So how do you imagine the fact that you guys are facing each other in a final.
to reflect on the type of game that we'll have today?
I would say that it doesn't count down.
A final.
It doesn't really matter the form that the teams are in, I think,
in a final because it's a game of emotions.
It's a game of little details.
So we'll see what happens.
How can you capitalize on the urgency that Arsenal has by not winning a trophy for so long?
Well, that's not something that we can control.
We can control our And we're going to, the only thing that we have to do is be ready,
perform as best as we can and win the title.
Four managers stand together tied for the record of four League Cup victories.
Alex Ferguson, Brian Clough, Jose Mourinho and Pep Guardiola.
Victory today will put Pep out on his own with a new record five Cup up wins.
I don't allow them to forget anything we have done.
We have done it in the past.
You prove that?
Why Through the middle.
Here's some cake.
I don't need to bring new cities.
Please.
This is the motto.
This is the challenge.
Expecting a big battle here in North London.
Here's our Sulk against Manchester City.
He's a massive, massive king.
You have to be ready.
Marbouch, why does it?
parmouch comes forward?
A real chance of arping for each?
I think we're forgetting the multi -wadding team.
You've written your orders here just on ourselves.
Show ourselves of death.
How much important to me in the end?
We have the men in for the video to.
You have considered me.
Otherwise I love you.
For we need to let it, the direction of the person from the party to the party.
But let's see, the light is the kind of the kind of the, because
they find a way of that to wear.
That's not.
How we do so.
That's That's.
Now it's time to hand over to the match as Manchester City take on Arsenal
in the 2026 Carabao Cup Cup final.